[
	{
		"question": "Which organ purify our blood?",
		"options": [
			"Kidney",
			"Heart",
			"Liver",
			"Lung"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "Which organ is capable of regeneration?",
		"options": [
			"Brain",
			"Heart",
			"Kidney",
			"Liver"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "What are the 3 types of blood vessels?",
		"options": [
			"Veins, nerves & skeletal system",
			"Arteries, veins & capillaries",
			"Arteries, lymph vessels & oesophagus",
			"Viens, nerves & oesophagus"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Heart is divided into right and left ______ and ________ .",
		"options": [
			"Atrium, Ventricle",
			"Epicardium, Endocardium",
			"Myocardium, Cohlea",
			"Bronchus, Bronchioles"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "What type of blood cells ward off infections?",
		"options": [
			"Platelets",
			"Plasma",
			"White Blood Cells",
			"Red Blood Cells"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the study of nerves called?",
		"options": [
			"Gastroenterology",
			"Pulmonology",
			"Angiology",
			"Neurology"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the biggest part of the brain called?",
		"options": [
			"Cerebrum",
			"Cerebellum",
			"Amygdala",
			"Brainstem"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "Which is the heaviest organ of the human body?",
		"options": [
			"Liver",
			"Brain",
			"Skin",
			"Heart"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "Which is the strongest part of the body?",
		"options": [
			"Bones",
			"Teeth",
			"Liver",
			"Heart"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "What is human hair made up of?",
		"options": [
			"Keratin",
			"Enamel",
			"Collagen",
			"Protein"
		],
		"answer": 0
	}
]